<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<source>
    <publisher>Chalmers Rekrytering</publisher>
    <publisherurl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/lediga-jobb/</publisherurl>
    <jobs>
        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Programmer at See/refine]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Fri, 24 Sept 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123123]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/en/job/see-refine-gothenburg-heltid-programmer-at-see-refine/;source=Indeed]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[See/refine]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <imageUrl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/Seerefine3555-350x350.jpg</imageUrl>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">About the Company:</h2> 
                <p>See/refine is a small and exciting international company with its office situated in Gothenburg. The company has just left the start-up phase and is growing rapidly.

                See/refine provide expertise in digital business transformation using a toolbox of IOT, machine learning in combination with modern web technologies. See/refine, among other things, builds mobile fleet management services for large service companies. Their platforms enables more than 100 people to work together in a simple and efficient way.

                What is important for See/refine is your personal development and you will get a lot of responsibility early so you can grow your knowledge and skills. </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the job:</font> 
                <p> The job is a full-time position as programmer at See/refine. As a member of the See/refine team you will work with development of hybrid apps and web applications which are based on the latest web technology. You will interact with hardware and manage large amount of data.

                Your work will range from understanding the customer’s requirements to development, test and release. Most of your work will be consultancy based and as an employee you will have a great chance to form and affect your own role and the company’s future. The company values work-life balance and has a two-week getaway to a foreign location every year. </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About you:</font> 
                <p> 
                We are looking for you who has an interest in programming and want to excel in your role. We believe that you already have some knowledge in programming but want to take your skills to the next level. As an individual you are ambitious, curious and likes to take responsibility. As your tasks will be consultancy based, we see you as communicative and solution oriented forming fantastic new services with See/refine’s customers.

                If you have any questions regarding the opening at Seerefine, please contact Alexandra Alto, alexandra.alto@chalmersrekrytering.se
                </p> 
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Sun, 31st October 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

        <job>
            <title><![CDATA[Junior Management Consultant]]></title>
            <date><![CDATA[Fri, 5 Sept 2021]]></date>
            <referencenumber><![CDATA[unique123124]]></referencenumber>
            <url>
                <![CDATA[https://chalmersrekrytering.se/en/job/signium-goteborg-stockholm-heltid-executive-research-consultant-pa-signium/;source=Indeed]]>
            </url>
            <company><![CDATA[Signium]]></company>
            <city><![CDATA[Gothenburg]]></city>
            <state><![CDATA[Västra Götaland County]]></state>
            <country><![CDATA[Sweden]]></country>
            <postalcode><![CDATA[412 58]]></postalcode>
            <imageUrl>https://chalmersrekrytering.se/wp-content/uploads/job-manager-uploads/company_logo/2021/09/33901988_545489335851461_6324058336534724608_n.jpg</imageUrl>
            <streetaddress><![CDATA[Sven Hultins Gata 9D,412 58 Göteborg]]></streetaddress>
            <description>
                <![CDATA[
                <h2 id="job_description">Do you want to be involved in developing Signium? We are growing and need to strengthen our teams in both Gothenburg and Stockholm:</h2> 
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Description of the Company:</font> 
                <p>Signium is an international partner-owned executive search / headhunting company with about 50 offices in 30 countries. We are continuously positioning ourselves as one of the 10 most reputable of the international leadership and chief recruitment companies.

                In Sweden, we have been operational since the start in 1981. Until 2016, we operated under the SIMS Executive Search brand. We have been connected and partners in our international network Signium since 1994.

                The Swedish operations are managed from three offices in Stockholm, Gothenburg and Malmö with a total of 18 people involved. At our offices in Gothenburg and Stockholm, we work just under ten people each per office. We are partner-owned and international, which enables us to work closely with our customers and adapt our processes to the customer's wishes, while at the same time enjoying the opportunity for the international platform that ownership in Signium provides.

                Read more about our company, consultants and approach to search at <url>www.signium.com</url> 
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">About the job:</font> 
                <p> We at Signium are experiencing a great demand for our services in the market. Not least, our customers have an optimistic view of the future now that we hope to see an end to the pandemic. That is why we hire new consultants and add new partners. In this growth journey, it means an increased need for support in our processes. We will therefore expand our team of researchers and look for you with experience in, for example, something in recruitment, talent sourcing, executive PA, service-related professions or as a journalist and you who have a great interest in people and business.

                This year, Signium celebrates 40 years in the Swedish market and we are Sweden's oldest Search company with a well-established customer base. This is our foundation, but we are also being modernized and digitized. We are looking for you who want to be with us on this journey. Having fun, acting professionally and with integrity and having the strength with the combination of the small entrepreneurial and the big global makes us well equipped to meet the increasing demand for our services. </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Description of the service:</font> 
                <p>
                As an Executive Research Consultant at Signium, you work in project teams together with senior consultants and have an important part in driving the projects forward. You are independently responsible for finding, attracting and evaluating candidates for our assignments. In the role of Executive Research Consultant, you actively participate in customer meetings both during sales and during the recruitment process and have many external contacts with both customers and candidates.

                We work with assignments with great variation regarding industry and positions, which means that with us you get the opportunity to broaden and deepen your knowledge of organizations and business. In the role of Executive Researcher, you are expected to keep up to date on industry changes and potential candidates.

                As an Executive Research Consultant, you are part of a team consisting of four researchers, but also have the opportunity to collaborate internationally in our practice group for researchers. We attach great importance to cooperation and encouragement. Our corporate culture is characterized by having high ceilings and having fun at work.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Your profile:</font> 
                <p>
                To succeed in the role, you need to have a drive, be creative and goal-oriented. Since you will have a large number of contacts daily, both internally and externally, it is important that you are communicative and relationship-building. We at Signium have a clear process for each individual customer, which requires that you have the ability to plan your time and work systematically.

                The role requires an analytical capacity and a good business understanding to understand the customer's needs and match candidates with the right challenge. As a person, you are independent and adaptable in the interaction with others. You are driven to achieve results and it is obvious for you to deliver with high quality.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">We are looking for you as:</font> 
                <ul>
                    <li>Gladly has an academic education, but no requirement</li>
                    <li>Gladly has experience from recruitment, but no requirement</li>
                    <li>Having experience of outreach / investigative activities is a great advantage</li>
                    <li>Has high digital ability / interest</li>
                    <li>With very good knowledge of Swedish and English</li>
                    <li>Is interested in Swedish and international business</li>
                    <li>Has a positive attitude and is used to working at a high pace</li>
                </ul>
                <p>
                It is important that you are attracted to working outward and outreach. The work involves customer contact with boards, CEOs and managers, which is why it is important that you feel comfortable discussing with people in leading positions from both Swedish and international companies.

                We offer an exciting and varied job where your work effort really makes a difference.
                </p>
                <font style="font-weight:bold">Application:</font> 
                <p>
                You are welcome to submit your CV by applying below. If you have any questions about the service, please contact: Alvin Leimo, alvin.leimo@hotmail.com.
                </p>
                
                ]]>
            </description>
            <jobtype><![CDATA[fulltime]]></jobtype>
            <expirationdate><![CDATA[Wed, 1st December 2021]]></expirationdate>
        </job>

    </jobs>
</source>
